Matheo Florez

Mississauga, ON Tel: (647) 297 6060 Email: mflorez1993@gmail.com

Emaii: miiorez1993@gmaii.com

About Me

Over 3 years of experience in Customer Service, Sales and Account Management the constant desire to continue learning and growing has always been present. My journey for programming began in late 2020 once I was introduced to creative projects built by a simple tutorial online. As a natural competitor who's always be involved in sports, I felt a compelling urge to compete with myself, and take on the challenge to learn code. Fast-forward to today and I'm still in competition despite many highs and lows through this journey, I continue living for this challenge.

Key Competencies

- HTML/CSS
- React
- JavaScript
- Material UI
- Intermediate coding ability with Visual Studio Code text editor
- Fluent in English and Spanish

- Tailwind CSS
- API Integration and GIT version control
- Effective communication ability
- Problem solving
- Proficient organizational skills
- Efficient with time-management

Work Experience

Self-Taught Front-End Developer

Udemy, FreeCodeCamp and Stack Overflow, Mississauga, Ontario

November 2020 - Present

- Largely focused on the JavaScript framework, React and component style programming for efficient project creation
- Learned principles such as Inheritance, Higher-Order functions and State management to aid in the build of reusable code
- Extracted API data via fetch requests, and utilized documentation to display information for user readability
- Designed CRUD based applications to demonstrate proficiency with data manipulation and storing it locally
- Experience with GIT and NPM for push requests resulting in improved project management and installation of packages for efficient application designs
- Developed an understanding of various styling libraries to aid in the production of a project build in a short time period

Customer Experience Associate

TD Canada Trust, Etobicoke, Ontario

June 2021 – Present

Processing sensitive financial transactions including withdraws, cheque and cash deposits

MATHEO FLOREZ

- Educating customers on the variety of accounts that may be a solution to their everyday banking requirements
- Thorough investigation of customer profiles to ensure validity and security, with the goal of assisting in the prevention of fraud or impersonation
- Relationship building with customers to understand client concerns, while providing a resolution in a timely manner
- Achievement of personal business objectives whilst working in unison with team members for overall team growth and success
- Performs efficient communication with colleagues for follow-up opportunities, which assists in the delegation of specified services

Maintenance Technician

Inside Care Facility Services, Mississauga, Ontario

September 2011 – May 2021

- Liaising with floor manager and superintendent for scheduled maintenance
- Mandatory inventory checks to ensure accurate product quantity requirements
- Punctuality for job site arrival and job time completion
- Relationship building with customer for job feedback and confirmation of completion
- Technical ability for equipment assembly and storage

Inside Sales Representative/Account Manager

January 2018 - September 2018

HP Canada Co, Mississauga Ontario

- Applied subject matter knowledge within established parameters to recommend products and alternatives, resulting in improved customer satisfaction.
- Leveraged using multiple tools and resources to aid in the solution of complex problem solving.
- Attentive to customers' needs and informs customer of product transitions, promotions and extended product services.
- Responsible for inputting data into specified software programs, allowing for improved management of various accounts and customer profiles.
- Adapted to working with various clients and built own sales funnel to create a daily selfmanagement work flow process.

Education

Honours Bachelor of Applied Science in Kinesiology

September 2011 - June 2015

University of Guelph-Humber

Diploma in Fitness and Health Promotion

September 2011 – June 2015

University of Guelph-Humber

Certifications

St. John Ambulance Standard First Aid – BLS CPR (HCP)

January 2020

Applied Suicide Intervention Skills Training

November 2018

References Available Upon Request